prudential financial full name
prudential financial group is an
american fortune 500 company
headquartered in new jersey founded in
1875 more than 140 years the company
mainly provides insurance investment
management funds and other financial
products and services with individual
and institutional customers in all the
united states and 40 more other
countries prudential is the largest
insurance company in the united states
with total assets of approximately
1.456 trillion dollars the main products
and services offered include life
insurance amenities funds pension and
retirement related investments
administrative and asset management and
securities brokerage services it
provides these products and services to
individual and institutional customers
through a distribution network in the
financial services industry
prudential operates in the us asia
europe and latin america and divide its
main business into financial services
and closed-end bulk businesses
redemption is made up of hundreds of
subsidiaries that have hold more than
four trillion dollar in life insurance
in
2019 pedestrian raised 20 million dollar
with a focus on blue collar areas and
did very well in 2020 prudential and
several of its investment companies
raised a second round of 70 million
dollars primarily to help some small and
medium-sized enterprises and white
collar workers of blue india understand
the importance of financial independence
and how to handle cash flow prudential's
unique customized product portfolio has
enough confidence to be recognized and
trusted by customers
prudential has the confidence to achieve
stable earnings for the company while
helping of blue-collar workers achieve
high returns and solving monthly
short-term cash flow shock for users
during the academic situation in india
in order to solve the india's people
savings investment and insurance needs
to help people in india have more
financial products and services during
the epidemic recovery period prudential
has developed a complete set of virtual
digital banking products prudential fund
investment fund is mainly used for
photovoltaic of new energy biological
medicine
5g industry research and development
chip manufacturing solar generate
electricity
as a fortune 500 company with more than
140 years of history prudential believes
you can make the most perfect wealth
distribution throughout the financial
planning and maximize your fortune